How do we measure the impact of a film?
Some measure it by its box office, but for me, the true impact of a film can be as simple
as a memorable line or a searing performance.
Over the decades, so many actors and supporting roles give us moments we will never forget.
I am in awe of Louis Gossip Jr. Sergeant Foley and an Officer in the Gentlemen.
Joel Gray's playfully menacing Ville Command in Gaboré
Denfills Heart Breaking Performance in Glory
The five men nominated this year as Best Supporting Actor have all made a significant impact
with vivid moments that will linger for many years to come.
Here are the nominees for performance by an actor in the supporting role.
Tom Hanks, a beautiful day in the name of the film.
The two men nominated this year as Best Supporting Actor have all made a significant impact
with vivid moments that will linger for many years to come.
I begin to realise that those films contain some of the most sophisticated storytelling
and all of cinema.
Their impact is extraordinary.
And I can't wait to introduce my daughter to this world now,
knowing it will take her imagination into directions that no one's even dreamed of yet.
See a Little Sure I spoke with her in subtitles
and I'm delighted to be back again.
Blue, Jinko, Goto, and Nurse Aroma.
Missing Lake, Chris Butler, Aryan, Sudnar, and Travis Night.
Joy Story 4, Josh Kool-Aid, and Mark Hinssen, and Jim Busra-Gara.
And Oscar goes to Joy Story 4.
Mark Hinssen, and Jim Busra-Gara.
This is the first Oscar in nominations for Mark Nielwood, the first Oscar in second nomination for Josh Kool-Aid.
The second Oscar in third nominations for John Swaphera.
We are so grateful for this honor.
We just went on a half-pretable cast and our crew on the Pixar Animation Studios.
We just want to thank the Academy for honoring our film alongside so many beautiful animated films this year.
We're just proud to be among them.
Listen, we take great pride in the fact that we get to make family films.
Joy Story 4 is really a love letter to our families.
This is for our parents, this is for our wives, this is for our kids.
We love you.
We want to thank the movie going on in so much, especially those that grew up with Joy Story.
We hope that your adventures with Woody and Buzz made drive not a little bit easier.
I love you so much.
Thank you.
And now here are the nominees for Best Animated Short Film.
Jisara Daria Kashayala.
Herelo, Matthew H.
Karen Burebatova.
Chippew, Tresana Sullivan, and Katherine Hepersen.
Memorable, brutal play, that is shown for so long before.
Sister, suchy, so.
And the Oscar goes to...
Karen Love.
And the Harry, the Harry, the Harry, the Harry, the Harry, the Harry.
This is the first Oscar in the nomination for Satellite Cherry in Karen from Prince Oliver.
Thank you so much for the Academy and everybody out there that supported this film.
There were lots of you that we share this award with you.
There were so many filmmakers that worked so hard on this and it was a labor of love.
And it was because we have a firm belief that representation matters deeply.
Especially in cartoons.
Because in cartoons that's when we first see our movies and it's how we shape our lives and think about how we see the world.
So I want to thank Sony Pictures Animation, you were the progressive people that believed in us from the beginning.
Christine Nelson, Jeff Korchak.
Thank you to a line for our animation to Six Point Harness and to Matthew Cherry.
Thank you to my beautiful husband, my son Chase and Miles for believing in me.
Thank you so much.
So, we have a big team and we have the thank for time as we're in the short.
So I just want to say that Harry Love was done because we wanted to see more representation in animation.
We wanted to normalize black hair.
There's a very important issue that's out there.
It's the Crown Act.
And we can help to get this person off in these dates.
It will help stories like the Andre Arnold, some of our special guests tonight stop to happen.
This award is dedicated to Kobe Bryant.
May we all have a second act as great as his voice.
Thank you.
Hello, Barry Kiano.
Anyway, it has been a long time since you and I made that movie.
That movie is something that Scott gave her.
Remember me?
You were a big fan of this movie.
I'll never forget for you.
I had a fancy Meyer screen with you.
Yeah, no, no.
No, no, no.
I mean, obviously, maybe there was a lot of crying in there.
I know lots of laughing and crying.
And we had some really...
Well, let me just be frank.
We have just written some lines.
But you and Chad, I wouldn't go that far.
But anyway, so how...
Yeah.
So far so that was surprising.
They were, this too.
I mean, that's really the power of a good script.
Am I right about that?
Absolutely.
I am okay.
So...
You're the nominees for Best Original Script.
Okay, I'm going to open this for you.
No, not yet.
That's what I mean.
Not yet.
I'm so written by Bryant Johnson.
All I've started to...
...is sitting in a chair by the fireballs in the boat.
To take the plane, use any investigations on the way.
You made a point of that.
Do you speak properly?
Mr. Wolf.
Mary Story written by Nolan Wolf.
Do not compare me to my father.
I mean, compare me to your dad.
I'm pretty glad that you were acting like him.
You're exactly like your mother.
Everything you're complaining about or you're doing.
You're suffocating him.
First of all, I love my mother.
She was a wonderful mother.
Pretty way, don't leave.
No, you leave.
How dare you!
I never leave mother and mother!
1917, written by Sam Mendez and Christine Wilson-Kan.
School field prize.
We see the burning town we're seeing behind him.
Well, let's crack off.
Once upon a time in Hollywood, written by Clint and Tarrantina.
I don't know your name, but I remember that here.
And you are, remember your wife, little face.
And you were on a forcing parasite.
Screams by Pong-June-Hole and Ham-June.
Storied by Pong-June-Hole.
Welcome to Pong-June-Hole.
Trist to retreat.
Then key new relunches toward Pong-June-Hole.
Then Goonsay after him.
And of course, Key-June has to jump after Goonsay.
Okay, and so the Oscar.
It goes to...
Oh my God.
Oh, shoot.
Screams is right.
This is the first Oscar at the third nomination in here for Pong-June-Hole.
The first Oscar nomination for Pong-June-Hole.
Thank you.
Great honor.
Writing a script is always such a lonely process.
We never write to represent our country.
But this is the first time I've ever written a script.
But this is the first Oscar at the third nomination.
Thank you.
Thank you for your great support and support.
I think my wife,
why for always being an inspiration to me,
I think all the actors who are here with me today for bringing this film to life,
thank you.
Thank you, Director Bo.
Thank you, my mom and thank you, Dad.
I have a lot of things to do in the States.
I have a lot of things to do in Korea.
As there's Hollywood in the US, in Korea, we have a lot of things to do in Korea.
Thank you for your great support and support.
I like to share this honor with all the storytellers and filmmakers at Chumurong.
Thank you, Director Bo.
Everybody comes to Riggs.
Shulish Jo.
Q&A.
Diversion.
But you may know them better as the films they became.
Casablan classic films.
This year's nominated writers have managed to capture the essence of their source material
in a way that is entirely unique and original.
Here this year's nominees for Best Adapted Screenplay.
The Irishman.
Screenplay by Steven Zalian.
The East of London.
I heard you made houses by Charles Brand.
You know who wants to get a leglin of service?
Some.
We chose some of the laundry businesses that's what they told me.
What about it?
Somebody else got an interest in that?
You know what I mean?
No.
I don't.
I am the other part.
And I know somebody who wants to get the other part.
Little women written for this screen are pretty much based on novel but it doesn't mean how good it is.
We interested in a story of domestic struggles and joys to have any people in the world.
It means it doesn't seem important that these people don't know what about them.
Our writing doesn't confirm what the set reflected.
We don't think so.
Writing will make them more important.
Joker.
Written by Todd Phillips and Scott Silver.
Based on characters created by Bob Gain, the figure, Jerry Rottes.
As the work loses on his new face, Arthur and Ab Joker dancing his way down the long staircase, doing his own bill, both jangles, rodents and stair-dads, skipping, twirling down steps, dancing and singing going to the music in his head.
Screenplay and re-time dancing.
They don't go dating with that, like a steam letter.
Excuse me.
Little girl.
Um.
You got one.
You.
I don't encourage his joe to continue.
The two popes.
Written by Anthony McCarthy.
Based on his play.
I got the feeling the person's up God.
I do not hear his voice.
Do you understand?
No, you must take it. You will have a step.
I believe in God. I think you got it.
Silence.
Any other words for you?
Tic-o-want-t-p.
This is the first Oscar in the number of these in the first title plays he's made.
Thank you.
Amazing. Thank you.
This is really nice.
This one's nice.
It's supposed to be heavy.
I'd like to thank my mother.
I believe I'm a lost you.
How was it?
I'm a lost you.
I was a good guy.
And I mean, for many other reasons.
But forget me the book.
And this film would have existed without you doing that.
Just Christine Barroning, thank you to the producers of the film, McCarthy Neil.
And Chelsea Winston-Danling was a reference to the beginning.
Thank you guys.
Many of you people don't want to thank me because I kind of remember them.
That's it.
This is really great.
I get a kind of...
Just can't serve the world to do that.
And dance.
And write stories.
We have original storytellers.
And we can make it to you as well.
Thank you for coming up.
Short films allow for new voices to be seen and heard without the constraints of budget or permission.
I've seen these films and they are beautiful.
And if you haven't seen it.
Come see it.
Thank you.
The reality.
The reality of the film is for best live action short films.
Brotherhood.
Mary M. Choupeur and Maria Garcia Turshant.
F. Depp of Oak Club, E.P.A. and Tommy and Megapink.
The neighbors window, Marshall Curry.
Sorry, Brian Buckley.
A sister, Delphine Jar.
Um...
The Oscars, calls to the neighbors window.
This is the first Oscar in four Sundays for Marshall Curry.
Wow, so grateful to all the people who made this film with me.
Including Maria Dizia, Julia John Wolfgang.
Listen to the producing partner, our kids, Jaina Rivers.
I want to dedicate this to my mom who grew up on a peach farm in Chesterfield, South Carolina.
It was the best storyteller I ever knew.
She always had a story about some crazy thing that happened with her siblings when she was growing up.
Or some weird dog that she had seen life that would break your heart.
And I learned from watching her that a well-told story is a powerful thing.
And it can change the way we see the world.
And it can help us to notice other people and care about those other people.
And maybe love each other a little bit more.
So, this is for her and for all the storytellers.
Hi, how are you?
Be honoring the work.
You know what?
Get to it.
Because we're upset.
Oh, are we upset?
You know what you guys don't want to know?
Frankly, I'm saying red.
I'm chipped off.
You know?
You know what you guys don't want to know?
You don't want that.
I'm chipped off!
Strange.
You know what?
I can't do this.
We're sorry.
We're too upset.
We're too upset to do this.
Sorry.
Guys, guys.
We're not mad at all.
That was an act.
We were acting.
We just know there are a lot of directors here tonight.
We just wanted the-
We did more than comedy.
Oh, that was my one.
Well, I guess it's my nose!
Son!
You were always gone when I was a kid.
You see, acting.
Something older than acting that works.
Question about the physical.
Production design.
You're looking at me.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
Do we have the credit to me?
Yeah, haha.
Here are the nominees for Continuing Production Design.
The Irishman Production Design by Bob Shaw.
Set Declaration by Regina Graves.
Jojo Rabbit.
Production Design by Robert Knatt.
Set Declaration by Nora Sopriva.
Team.
Production Design by Dennis Gausner.
Set Declaration by Louis Santé.
Once upon a time in Hollywood, production designed by Barbara Lee set decoration by Nancy Hayes.
Parasite, production designed by Keith.
And the Oscar goes to...
Oh, it seems.
Once upon a time in Hollywood...
This is the first Oscar in nominations for Marvel's play, The Second Oscar and the Eighth Combination for Nancy Hayes.
Thank you to the Academy.
And thank you, and we share this with our incredible art department and my partner in crime, Decorator Nancy Hayes.
Mostly to Quintaritino, for writing an epic masterpiece and letting us take this wild ride with him.
Thank you.
A huge shout out to all the people that helped us here tonight.
The craftsmen, the construction guys, the painters, our prop master Chris Call.
And of course my gang, Mark and Sarah and Joensie and Adam and everybody.
I appreciate it so much.
Thanks for joining us.
Well, I have a doctor's appointment.
Okay, the nominees for Best Costume Design.
Wait, wait, that's it?
We can't skip right to the award.
You're right.
You're right so much because I'm a costume designer.
What else should we say?
Well, maybe we don't say it.
Maybe we sing it.
Please, who's on made for walking?
And that's just what they'll do.
And one of these days these boots are going to look all over.
You can look, you can look.
Don't tell me crooked and mouth up is bull.
Step with a blue dress, blue dress, blue dress, double with a blue dress.
Oh, blue, very real.
Fuff, fuff, fuff, fuff, we've read a lot of them.
And I know, D-check and the committee.
Be as dancing with me.
Sheep to cheek, sheep to cheek, and a thong, thong, thong, thong.
You can hear the battle.
Here are the nominees for achievement and costume design.
The Irishman, costume design by Sandy Powell and Christopher Peterson.
Jojo Rabbit, costume design by Lyos Save and Reveille.
Joker, costume design by Mark Bridges.
Little women, costume design by Jacqueline Daring.
Once upon a time in Hollywood, costume design by Ariane Phillips.
And the Oscar goes to Jacqueline Durand Little Women.
This is the second Oscar in seven nominations for Jacqueline Durand.
Thank you.
Thank you to the Academy.
I'm indebted to another people to a wonderful team to an amazing cast.
I'm a cast, a producer, Amy Pesco.
To my family, who had able me to be a working mother.
And first and last, to Greta Goeweak.
She was an inspiration to all of us.
This year's nominated document.
It was a wonderful season.
Here are the nominees for Best Documentary Feature.
American Factory, Steven Polcar, Julia Blankert and Jeff Blankert.
What we're doing is we're making two cultures together.
The Chinese culture and the US culture.
The cave, the fused fire, the kidney, the Margaret, Steven Blankert.
The Asian democracy.
And the Oscar goes to American Factory.
This is the first Oscar and second nomination for Steven Polcar.
Thank you
Wow, thank you.
Well, even before that envelope got opened, just being in the presence in the company of our
sister and brother, documentarians.
Oh, Chris, who is their lives?
Ah, making stories, bringing stories to us about hospitals being bombed in Syria, about
Brazil, about Macedonia.
We were so proud.
We are inspired by you guys.
Our film is from Ohio and China.
Go, guys, and, um, sorry.
And what it really could be from anywhere that people put on a uniform, a punch-a-clock,
trying to make their families have a better life.
Working harder and harder these days.
And we believe that things will get better when workers of the world unite.
Thank you, Academy.
Thank you to everyone who trusted us to tell your story.
Shesh-shesh, how to wag.
Thank you to our unstoppable crew, our beloved friends and family.
Each and John, each elite, our unstoppable editor, Lindsay Hughes.
And to those big-hearted people like Netflix, Participant Media, Higher-Rain Productions,
and the tough, inventive, great people of Dayton, Ohio.
And now, here are the nominees for Best Documentary, Short Subject.
I think there's some to do some June during the young circle.
Learning to skateboard in a horse of a year ago.
The title is, I'm going to wait.
Life over Shakespeare, John Hampton, and Christine Jameson.
Walk around Chacha, or a next-and-colette sandstone.
And the winner is...
Learning to skateboard in a horse of a year ago.
This is the first Oscar, and I'll be using it for a funeral autograph and a later award.
Shesh-shesh.
Oh my God.
Oh no.
You can't see anything.
I am Frank Capra.
You guys remember Frank Capra handed me a Student Academy Award in 1977.
And I thought I'd skip the hard part.
I thought I would and go on to make movies.
And if I hadn't had that encouragement at my backpack then,
I wouldn't have been able to withstand the last four decades in this business.
I want to thank any any films and Muldik Thompson,
Green Media, to add a Michelinel, the man behind the women,
the brilliant, my Lisa Rinsler, cinematographer, and Mary Mannhart, editor extraordinaire,
to Zama and Tan Ayazzy, our number one girl crew.
I've been working in Afghanistan since 2005, and this movie is my love letter,
to the brave girls of that country.
To get to Capra from here took a whole lot of not quitting and teachers.
The kind I strive to be at and where you film school and the kind of teachers at Skatestand School
at the heart of the film.
They teach girls courage to raise your hands.
Here, I have something to say, and I'm going to take that ramp.
Don't try to stop me.
Thank you very much.
Keep getting so far!
Most of the actors and actor I know, most about a lasting body of work,
choosing roles that do more than just speak to them personally,
but with the hope of their performance, who resonate with others.
If I have one, it's nominated.
The supporting actress of Judd Nung just that.
The idea of a good father was only invented like 30 years ago.
We love them for their fanlabilities, but people absolutely don't accept those same feelings and matters.
You want to be there, you?
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
I'll talk to you later, I'll get you.
Richard is not a murderer.
He saved people's lives.
Mr. President, please clear.
This team of murder living for our two support my family.
And if we had children, they would be his outline.
You said, don't sit there and tell me that marriage isn't an economic proposition because it is.
I can't call anyone else when I just, I need someone right now to tell me that that's what I should do.
Do you keep defending these people?
I'm not a friend of a new home to destroy them.
I feel sorry for you, I really do.
I feel sorry for me, I mean, for the same way one day.
You know, let me respect you if I can be loved.
And I know anything about being a murderer.
You know, I tell you in the eye, entrust without fear that's what it is to be a murderer.
I have a kid from my ex, and some of my sister's heart is.
And I'm not a real abusive.
I would have been nice if somebody told us they'd be there after more than a length.
Nobody's drawn to protect you, PLN.
That's all I've ever done.
Here are the number of these.
It's my actions in a supporting role.
Kathy Bates, Richard Jewel.
We're there, very stories.
Scott and Jill Hanson, Jill Joe Brett.
The floor is beautiful, little one.
The rock of the bombshell.
And I ask for those two.
Lord, dear, may I ask for your name?
It's my first townscarf, and there's no reason for the floor and dirt.
We're about to出 for our attacks.
Thank you to the Academy for his honor of being in this room with such remarkable artwork, artists going on.
My family's, my sisters and colleagues.
Thank you Netflix. My friend Ted Scott everyone for their support and love to Noah his vision his magic
Thank you Noah for your words and for your friendship and art and life with you and Greta
Thank you to this cast and majestic Adam Scarlett Ellen Ray, our amazing crew David Noah wrote a movie about love
and about breaching divisions in the name and in the honor of family and home and hopefully for all of us in the name of our planet
and I stepped my stepchildren CJ and Harris my heart and inspiration
yeah and you know some say never meet your heroes but I say if you're really blessed you get them as your parents
I share this with my acting heroes my legends diet lab and Bruce Dern
You got him I love you thank you all for this gift into the best Bruce Day present ever
I love you I love my friend he lift me up every day
I can now officially say that I've held a lost girl on this stage congratulations not the way to
I win the seemingly impossible task of sound editors is to immerse the viewer in a world day and we first am
these years nominees have vividly brought to life first world war changes the man's in range of the city of Gotham
the lanans race track and even a galaxy far far away I'm yet so close here are the nominees for achievement in sound editing
forward versus Ferrari Donald Soplester
Joker Alan Robert Murray
1917 Oliver Tarni and Rachel Tink
Once upon a time in Hollywood
Riley Steve
ツ
Andy Oscar coast
Kevin
Four of those is for our reason. It is a marriage of sound and picture. So while I'm
reading on a thank-you, fantastic sound, team, I also want to include the picture team in
the mixers. In fact, four yet, four of those are for our. It's probably the last film
I made by 20th Century Fox. So Leon and I will watch. But the real support comes from
home, so I want to thank my wonderful wife of 34 years. A game of her editing career,
for me to pursue micro-review. And how she raised our kids, and she did a great job
because neither one of them are politicians. For the real reason I'm standing here, so
James Mangle, he is the reason I'm here. He should have been nominated for our best director.
So if I could, I'd break this statue off and give him the hand so you could put it in
the jargum. Thank you, Kathy.
And now here are the nominees for achievement in sound mixing.
At Astra, Gary Wright Strong, Tom Johnson and Marquiland.
Four versus Ferrari, home-massing David Yamako and Steven A. Mal.
Oh, my God, John, Tom Othagic, Dean Supers, and Tom Lee.
1917, Martin A. Stewart Wilson.
What's up on the time in Hollywood? Michael Minker, Christian P. Minker and Marquiland.
And the Oscar goes to 1917, Martin A. Stewart Wilson.
This is the first Oscar, a third nomination for Martin A. Stewart.
This is the first Oscar, a third nomination for Steven A. Stewart Wilson.
This award on behalf of the entire 1917 team, each one of them did outstanding work on this film from my guys in the trenches to Marques' team in the studio.
For their incredible support, thanks to our families, Victoria Ava and to our producers, Kamen, Jane Anand and Pippa.
And Sam Anderson, none of us would be here without you. Thank you.
I'd like to thank all of you, this great team, Rachel, Mike Ventan, Jambou.
Lisa Smith, I read it, all the guys who gave us such a great school to work with.
Roby and the guys are go grist, Rob Carlson.
Two-year-old Louis drivers and I have made multiple films and have had an enormous amount of experience on film sets.
We certainly understand the importance, indeed, the primacy of the cinematographer to film.
Not only does the cinematographer prepare the meals for the crew and cast.
He is also the cinematographer who knocks on your trailer door to let you know that it is time to get to the set to create magic.
And it is the cinematographer and only the cinematographer who is waiting patiently for you in that golf cart to travel you to set.
Oh, how splendid, man, to honor these unsung cinematic heroes.
Wait, wait, I'm sorry, I'm being told that that is not the role of the cinematographer.
And it has something to do with camera.
Who is talking to you?
I have no idea.
To exit, you not have any earpiece?
Hello?
No, I don't think anything is in there.
Here are the nominees for achievement in cinematography.
The Irishman, Rodrigo Puyatello.
Joker, Lauren Scherren.
The lighthouse, Sharon Blaschke.
1917 Roger Finkens.
Once upon a time in Hollywood, Robert Richardson.
Pretty cute.
And the Oscar goes to Roger Deacon's site.
Name between French and South American.
Name between French and Seagull.
Thank you.
I want to thank my fellow nominees for their wonderfully inspiring work.
But more than that, I want to thank them for their friendship too.
I'm pretty good cook actually.
This belongs to a lot of people who worked on this movie.
It belongs to my wife James, who worked on it.
It belongs to my assistant and focus bullet-hardy Harris who is somewhere on there.
There is the ember wizard of Bugs Pulling.
And you'll never know what he does.
Because he only knows that he makes a mistake and he never does.
It's to be the cover crew, to ensure...
Fantastic operators.
It's to Gary Hems, a grip crew, and John Higgins, Biggles.
He's bringing my friend for about 30 odd years, who is Agatha.
So to them, I know that wonderful team.
And I think they would all want me to say thank you Sam Mendis for the most wonderful experience.
Thank you.
We'll never forget it.
So, you know, Louis Drivers and I have made multiple films.
And I've had an enormous amount of experience on film sets.
We certainly understand the importance, indeed, the primacy of the rule of the cinematographer to film.
Not only does the cinematographer prepare the meals for the crew and cast.
He is also the cinematographer who knocks on your trailer door to let you know that it is time to get to the set.
Imagine.
And it is the cinematographer and only the cinematographer who is waiting patiently for you in that golf cart to travel you to set.
Oh, how splendid.
Then to honor these unsung cinematic heroes.
Wait. Wait.
I'm sorry, I'm being told that...
What?
...that is not the rule of the cinematographer.
Oh.
And it has something to do with camera.
Oh. Who is stopping you?
I have no idea.
They just gave me a earpiece.
I said, do you not have a earpiece?
Hello?
No, I don't think anything is in there.
Okay.
Here are the nominees for achievement in cinematography.
The Iron Man.
We go free at home.
Joker.
Lauren Scher.
The lighthouse.
Jiren Blaschke.
1917.
Roger.
Thank you.
Once upon a time in Hollywood, Robert Richard's 7th.
And the Oscar goes to Roger Deacon's site.
The nomination for Roger Deacon.
Thank you, well.
I want to thank my fellow nominees for their wonderfully inspiring work.
Thank them for their friendship, too.
I'm pretty good cook, actually.
This belongs to a lot of people that worked on this movie.
It belongs to my wife James, who worked on it with me.
It belongs to my assistant and focus bulletin.
And the Harris, who is somewhere right there.
Who is the ember wizard of focus bullet?
And you'll never know what he does.
And you don't need no scissors.
He makes a mistake and he never does.
It's to Peter Cover, who's in charge of the risk.
It's not to fantastic operators.
It's to Gary Hems, a great crew, and John Higgins Beagles.
He's been my friend for about 30 odd years, who's a gaffer.
So it's to them and all their wonderful team.
And I think they would all want me to say thank you so much.
The most wonderful experience.
Thank you. We'll never forget it.
Okay, so that was the cinema time.
Yes.
Our next category is film editing.
We know all about film editors.
They're the ones who like to cut out a lot of my lines.
Oh yeah.
They did a real number on me this year.
Did you know that I was originally in 1917?
No.
Yeah, I'm parasite.
Oh my god.
Wonderful.
I know.
Well, listen to this.
It was originally Ford versus Ferrari versus Ferrell.
What?
Yes.
And I'm still a lot of the key art.
Unbelievable.
I'm just going to say I hate this one.
Oh yeah, it's almost the same.
It's the same.
I'm just going to say it.
I'm going to say it.
It's almost the same.
It's an old hole.
Old hole.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
No, no.
So you do have one of you?
Yeah.
Oh no, he's about to say it on me.
He's saying it.
There's no nominees for achievement in film editing.
Yeah, he just did it.
Ford versus Ferrari.
I'm going to say it.
Joe Joe Ravitt.
Tommy Eels.
Joe Mica.
Jeff Rose.
Oh.
You're sorry.
You're on the jet.
And the Oscar goes to Michael McCusker and Andrew Buckwood.
This is the first Oscar in nomination for Phantom Booklets.
This is also the first, we're in the end second,
the Venetian for Michael McCusker.
Hello.
I like to think they counter me into all the fellow nominees.
Incredible work.
We wouldn't be here without our stellar picture crew and our outstanding sound team as well.
It's my amazing and beautiful wife Maria and our son Lucas.
I love you so much.
Thank you very much.
To my sister Claire and Joe and to our mom,
to my mom and dad who supported me from the very beginning.
I love you so much.
I'm in my family in Argentina.
And I'm very, so good on you.
James Mangel.
I just, it's my great pleasure to have sat and watched you become one of the best directors in this business in the last years.
Thank you so much.
Thanks for your great ensemble, Matt, and Christian,
our TP, Faden, Pop and Michael, our producers,
Janet Topper and Peter Churren,
to everyone at 20th century.
The tireless Aaron Downey,
Take Goliato, Steve Aswell,
and the inimitable Emma Watts.
And finally, it's my daughter, Helena.
I love you so much.
I love you, Lava.
Thank you so much for just listening.
Please welcome,
Christine Durender and Academy President, David Greenhead.
So this event is the highlight of the Academy's year.
There's another milestone coming up in the very near future.
I hear some history for you.
In 1929, the Academy's leaders decided to open up a museum.
That was under the leadership of my presidential predecessor,
Douglas Fairbanks.
As you can imagine,
only one of a million ways I've been linked to Douglas Fairbanks.
Well, now, after a mere nine decades,
we are about to do Mr. Fairbanks proud
with a special announcement.
But in their time and their effort to make a reality
of this state-of-the-art showcase of the movie making.
And here's one of the museum's greatest champions,
Joe Chimellas, your winner, Tom Hanks.
Go, Joe.
Joe Chimellas!
Hello, David.
There is plenty of culture to be found.
There are many city vangels.
There are museums dedicated to art, music and history, and science.
And we even have a museum dedicated to selfies
I'm not sure why, but there it is.
You look it up and enjoy, I guess.
But there's never been a museum dedicated to the art of science as emotion pictures.
But it is being born. This labor of love, a bunch of us were over there just this morning.
I was putting up some drywall.
I saw the New Hanson and Robert Horbiddle Sand.
Great, it was on the roof working with a shirt on.
As was Colin Joost, and dude that was no contest.
The world very proud of what has been accomplished so far in the landmark that is taking shape at Fairfax and Wilshire.
That is Fairfax and Wilshire.
And it is a pleasure to announce that the Academy of Music and Emotion Pictures will open its doors on December 14th of 2020.
As Cosmenders of the Motion Hitchhickhats.
Nobody more than us understands the importance of good visual effects.
Here are the nominees for achievement in visual effects.
And here is the award winner for the award winner.
The award winner is the Oscar winner of the award winner.
The award winner is the Oscar winner of the award winner for the award winner.
Here are the nominees for achievement in facial effects.
Avengers Endgame, Dan DeLue, Russell Lill, Matt Bacon, and Dan Seudick.
The Irishman, Pablo Hilton, Leandro Estavegarena, Nelson Sepulveda Falza, Estefan Broadly.
The Lion King, Robert Lugato, Adam Beldes, Andrew Rogers, and Elliot Newman.
1917, Keon Rusharone, Greg Butler, and Dominique Tuyi.
Star Wars, The Rise of Skywalker, Roger Goyer, Neil Scanlon, Patrick Tuyi, and Dominique Tuyi.
Anthony!
On the Oscar goes to... 1917!
This is a second Oscar and second nominated for the Field Prochoral and first weighted second nominated for the Great Classar and the first weighted third nominated for the Domina II.
1917!
Thank you for the uncounting for this tremendous honor. 1917 is what you call a dream project.
An opportunity to challenge or be approach visual effects, but also a chance to collaborate with some truly fantastic people.
Thank you to some members, and leading us through this big journey.
I want to thank producers, B. Bach, Chen Anan, and Carmen, and everybody at the Emily and the Universal for your collaboration and supports.
Thank you to my beautiful wife, Gates, for standing there right by me in every step of the way.
And I want to thank the team of 600 artists at MPC and also fantastic special effects team. We share this award with you.
Thank you.
Thank you all. Thank you so much.
Peter, thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Good evening. We're here to present the award for makeup and hair styling.
It's impossible to overstate the role that hair and makeup play in the craft of filmmaking.
Case in point, I'm 87 years old.
And I'm Charlize Theran.
As actors, our transformation starts in the makeup and hair.
Listen, I'm all joking aside. I do want to say I saw firsthand how talented hair and makeup people are in the Irishman.
They would transform us every day. I would just sit there and be amazed.
And then Pudgy would come in and say...
I think they're going to believe that. Not everything is Netflix, right?
I got care.
Everyone will go there.
Here are the wonderfully talented artists nominated this year for a cheap and makeup and hair style.
Boneshell, Castle Hero, Anne Morgan and Vivian Baker.
Joker, Mickey Laterman, and Kate George.
Jimmy, Jeremy Woodhead.
Malatica 7, Vistress of Evil, Paul Gooch, Orientite and David Woodhead.
1917, Naomi Don, Tristan Ruslas, Emma Vocacola, Andy.
And Vios.
Boneshell, Anne Morgan and Vivian Baker.
This is the second Oscar in fourth nomination for the first Oscar in nomination.
Thank you very much. It's a great honor.
And we would like to thank members of the Academy in Director J. Lodge and Charles Landau of Bobgrave,
Karen Beto, Mescolo, AJ Dix, Michelle Blurr and Dave Johnson and the entire team at the firm studio and Lionsgate.
And the cast include and friends and family for their amazing support and my mentors Rick Baker and Dixson.
And we would like to give our heartfelt thanks to Sherry Sel, you're amazing.
You are amazing actor and producer and your compassion and love and care made this film possible.
And because of your bravery and passion, we are able to set the new in the makeup industry and creating this film.
Bruce, thank you very much and we will present the film.
We wouldn't be getting this award without you.
Coming up, the Malatica series and Elton John performs rock and roll bands. I'm gonna love me again.
And then later, the Oscars for directing, rest actors and actors and rest fixtures.
The Oscars on TVC, the most you buy has a lot of stuff.
Good evening. I'm here as a nominees for the Fashion International Feature Film.
From Poland, Gorbos Christi, directed by Jan Pomasa.
From North Macedonia, Honila, directed by Lucia Tupano, Antamara, Gordesca.
From France, Memy Selhad, directed by Lashley.
Bain and glory, directed by Bain and Lodovania.
From South Korea, Parasite, directed by Lucia Tupano.
On the other side, goes to Parasite.
And it's the first movie from South Korea to Vietnam, and it's a big Oscar.
The category has a new name now from Best F...
International Feature Film. I'm so happy to be at first recipient under the new name.
The name is Anzac Arun, and it's a lot inside.
The category has a new name now from Best F...
International Feature Film. I'm so happy to be at first recipient under the new name.
The name is Anzac Arun, and it's a lot in support, the new direction that this change symbolizes.
We have a lot of experience with this movie.
The director of the love story, Lee Sun-kyun Choi Woo-shik, Jang Yixin.
The director of the love story, Lee Jung-hoon Park.
Food and drink.
ладно, we're great. We're able to champion our onward actress and supporting him.
Good to meet you.
That's it for today.
And thank you all for your support and support.
Thank you everyone for your support and support.
Thank you and I'm ready to drink tonight.
Thank you.
And the Oscar goes to Hymnur.
This is the first Oscar in the elimination of our food and stuff over here.
Wow.
This is so touching.
Thank you.
My best friend, my other set of ears, I'd be lost without you.
My mother, my son, Cody, I can't see you.
I love you so much.
To the girls, to the women, to the mothers, to the daughters.
We'll hear the music bubbling within.
Please speak up.
We need to hear your voices.
Last time on a stage, I'm on a Jumbo T'N'Hars.
My moral is brolemets and simile Jackson.
And thank God he had dropped me.
Stand by here tonight for the nominees for Sheetland and Direct.
The Oscar says he, the Irishman, Todd Phillips Joker.
He said Mendez, 1917.
The Oscar, Quentin Tarantino, close one of time, and hug.
Tom Juneho, Harrison.
Tom Juneho.
Thank you.
Today's the last day of the year.
After winning Best International Feature, I thought I was done for the day and was ready to relax.
Thank you so much.
When I was young in studying cinema, there was a saying that I carved deep into my heart, which is the most personal as the most creative.
I come out of bed, cut to us from our great artist courses.
I studied Marti English and studied English.
When I was in school, I studied Martin Scorsese's film.
It was a huge honor. I never thought I would win.
I still love the audience and the audience.
When people in the US were not familiar with my film, when I always put my films on his list, he's here.
Thank you so much.
I'm so honored to be with you.
Thank you.
I will drink until the next morning.
I'm winning enough to get any tissue.
Last year was the best night of my husband's life.
I've been in both three times.
I hope you're all having as good a time as he did.
I don't want to keep you from the bar much longer.
I know I'm supposed to talk about acting and find some clever thread to connect these performances, but their beauty and brilliance surely lies in the fact that there is one.
I'm sorry. I'm counting.
You know what I'm saying to you?
You just ask the same questions every week.
As your child.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I think it's getting a little bit more.
It'll certainly turn around.
There are no other friends.
This is the thing.
It needs to know that I've gone for him.
I've used the Facebook.
Failure that is your career.
We're crying about it.
I don't want to be in some sense.
It's yet to come to the conclusion that the goals is facing facing mercy.
Mercy is the time that might have to close down on both.
What's happening with the evil people there?
He's coming to terms with what it's like to be slightly more.
Use.
Come to the religion.
You know what you're doing.
You always make one a ton of care.
You know what you do with your own company.
I don't know why everyone is so rude.
I don't want anything from you.
Maybe a little bit of war.
Maybe a hotbed.
Boom.
Every day I wake up real in your tent.
Just like if I can do it.
See I'll re-review.
I don't care if you're gonna kill us.
And I can get by the dark and dark.
Make a grand jibby's.
I remind you.
And to this maybe I don't.
But I love.
It is a better one.
I'm scared.
I'll clear all the nominees for Pull chilly.
Take a lady called.
I'm Turnia Ben Darius.
Viewing.
Danny.
Suddenly there is a caprio with a tie and shoulder.
Tony.
Adam.
variant story.
Walking remix.
So, okay.
I think I'll skip those two.
Waking Phoenix, okay.
The first answer is
if somebody's in for 14 Phoenix.
But,
so, so much.
Got a move so much better to go to my home.
And I do not feel elevated up of any of my fellow anomalies or any one of this room
because we share the same love, the love of film.
And this form of expression has given me the most extraordinary loss.
I don't know what I'd be without it.
But I think the greatest gift that it's given me and many of us in this room
is the opportunity to use our voice for the voiceless.
I've been thinking a lot about.
So, the distressing issues that we are facing collectively.
And I think we feel or remain to feel that we champion different causes.
But for me, I see commonality.
I think whether we're talking about gender inequality or racism
or queer rights or indigenous rights or animal rights.
We're talking about the fight against injustice.
We're talking about the fight against the belief that one nation, one people, one race, one gender.
But one species has the right to dominate, control and use, exploit, and other with impunity.
I think that we've become very disconnected from the natural world.
And many of us, what we're guilty of is an agicentric world view.
The belief that we're the center of the universe, we go into the natural world
and we plunder it for its resources.
We feel entitled to our deficient disseminated cow.
And when she gives birth, we steal her baby, even though her cries of anguish are unmistakable.
And then we take her milk that's intended for a calf.
And we put it in our coffee and our cereal.
And I think we fear the idea of personal change.
Because we think that we have to sacrifice something to give something up.
But human beings at our best are so inventive and creative and ingenious.
And we think that when we use love and compassion as our guiding principles,
we can create development, implement systems of change that are beneficial to all sentient beings and to the environment.
I've been selfish, I've been cruel at times, hard to work with, and I'm grateful.
But so many of you in this room have given me a second chance.
And I think that's when we're at our best when we support each other out from past mistakes.
But when we help each other grow, when we educate each other, when we guide each other towards redemption,
that is the best of humanity.
I just want to...
When we...
When we was...
When we was 17, my brother grew up with this leg.
He said, run to the rescue with love and peace will follow.
Thank you.
Here are the nominees for performance by an actress in a leading role.
Cynthia Rivo, Aryan's.
The Lajohansson Marriage Store.
So she wrote it, little women.
She released their own home show.
Renizo Waker, Judy.
We also have those two.
Renizo Waker.
I'm fighting me here alongside one of the most special collaborations and meaningful experiences of my life.
I've said it before and I'm going to say it again.
Cynthia, Scarlett, Charlize, Sarsh, I have to say, a way it is an honor to be considered in your company.
David Livingstone, Cameron Kraken, director of your group of goals.
It was a privilege to work with you.
I feel so proud to be in your beautiful movie.
I've got to thank my stage mom.
Matt, Paul Gary, Jesse Buckley, Finway Rock, Griffiths Soul, Altcast, and the crew who worked so hard on this film to celebrate Judy Garland.
Mike Stendard family at CAA Peter Brown, I am a pianist.
I'm a pianist.
Nancy Ryder, thank you for the 25 years.
John Carabino, my handsome date of 25 years.
Thank you for always dreaming bigger than I would dare.
And for bringing it back to the work and joy and gratitude.
My immigrant folks who came here with nothing but each other and have believed in the American dream.
How about this?
Thank you to you, Big Brother Drew, Randy, Judy, Stone, and Eva for all the love and support possible that makes you believe anything is possible.
And I have to say that this past year of conversations celebrating Judy Garland across genders and I mean, so I'm sorry, as a questioner,
I'm not sure if you're interested in the cross-section culture, it's been a really cool reminder that our heroes unite us.
Now, as to find the best in ourselves, when we look to our heroes, we agree.
And that matters.
Neil Armstrong, Sally Ride, Delores Hurtz, Venus and Serena and Selena, Bob Dylan, Scorsey Z, Fred Rogers, Harriet Tubman.
We agree on our teachers and we agree on our courageous men and women in uniform who serve, we agree on our first responders and firefighters.
And when we celebrate our heroes, we, you know, we're reminded of who we are as one people united.
And now, Judy Garland did not receive this honor in her time.
I am certain that this moment is an extension of the celebration of her legacy that began on our film set.
Also, representative of the fact that her legacy of unique exceptionalism and inclusivity and generosity of spirit, it transcends anyone, artistic achievement.
Ms. Garland, you are certainly among the heroes of the United States and to find us.
And this is certainly for you.
I am so grateful.
Thank you so much everybody.
Coming up next, the final award of receiving the Academy Award for Best Picture is the Oscars on ABC.
Thank you very much.
Nothing is more important than raising awareness, right?
Tonight, we've hopefully brought to light the impact that films have made and can make on our lives as individuals and on society as a whole.
For the Academy, here are the films that made the greatest impact this year.
Ready?
There are a few people who find something they have to do. Some of them they can't do it.
They don't know how to wait out of their mind.
Come, I can't wait out.
I can't wait out.
Forward versus Ferrari.
Peter Chardonnay, General Topping and James Lannold for this year's.
He's got a pretty good friend.
And some people having serious problems with it.
We're going to move on with these things.
Right now, we're in the same room.
We're going to move on these things.
We are Richmond, Martin Scorsese, Robert De Niro, James Wilson, and Emma Dillinger, Cosco, producers.
We're not in that scene.
I'm not supposed to be in the scene.
I think that's a pretty good sign right now.
Do not!
Don't be tired!
We're in the poster house.
I wanted to post my journal in the brain around the time.
Definitely, it knows a good time to be an on-state.
Jojo Revan, Arthur Neil, Tyco YG, and Chelsea Winstead, over the stars.
The stars are Jojo, what are you doing?
I don't think it's with you, Croix.
I've met my own motor, I've decided that I've been in there.
That takes up a triad of police.
How do you know you would just have to help police?
Do what you deserve.
Joker, Todd Phillips, and Bradley Knollard, and Emma Dillinger, Cosco, producers.
And women, we have minds, and we have souls, as well as just dogs.
And they've got ambition, and they've got...
Let's just beauty, and I'm so sick of people not saying that love is just all of women.
It's a thing for I'm so sick of it, little women.
Amy Pascale, producer.
You're my baby, Harry.
First, I'll never get to really be a star, it's a girl.
It'll be different, they'll exist.
You really want me to switch it, I love you.
I'm gonna have to do it, though, right?
You're so merged with your own selfishness.
You don't need an identified and selfishness anymore.
Marriage story.
Oh, oh no, oh no.
1917, Sam Lenders, and the Harris, Jane Ann Hedmer, and Calvin McDermott, producers.
So, you're a genius, a perfect girl, and you're rich in the truth.
You are a devil, and I'm here to defend dance.
Now, Summer, you have lots of fun and time and Hollywood, David Heyman, Shannon McIntosh, and Quentin Tarantino, producers.
Okay.
David, don't you see, in the middle of the night, I'm not gonna leave that alone.
You're too cute to come to.
Parasite, Quentin A, and Pondromo, producers.
And the Oscar goes to...
Parasite.
The Harris by the end takes a heavy effort, not a big deal.
And it's the first film, something very much like we do.
Sure, we need more Oscars tonight.
I'm gonna play the music.
Oh, yeah, I'm so...
I'm speechless.
We never imagine this to ever happen.
So happy.
It's happening right now.
I'm so happy.
We never imagine this to ever happen.
I express my deepest gratitude and respect for all the members of the Academy
for making this decision.
Thank you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hi everybody.
I really want to thank Crist the результат button.
Thank you.
Thank you for being new and I like everything about him. He smiles, he's crazy hair, the way he talks, the way he walks, and especially the way he directs.
And what I really like about him is his sense of humor and the fact that he can be really making fun of himself and he never takes himself seriously.
Thank you, thank you very much.
I'd like to thank everybody who's been supporting Parasite and who's been working with Parasite and who's been loving Parasite.
And I'd like to thank my brother who's been always supporting our building our dreams.
Even when it looked impossible dream, thank you Jay. I want to thank my brother Jay. And especially I really really really want to thank our Korean film, others, our movie wars, who's been really supporting all our movies and never hesitated to give us straights for an opinion on what they feel like their movies.
And it made us really never be able to be complacent and keep pushing the directors, the creators, keep pushing the envelopes.
And without you, our Korean film audience, we are not here. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.